<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sam Braza</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sam Braza</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021
</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 22:52:56 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Samuel Braza</title>
      <link>/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/about/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Sam Braza. I created this site to post some of my ideas in philosophy, as well as to show some of the things I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on. I graduated in 2020 from Santa Clara University with degrees in philosophy and biochemistry. I am actively pursuing biomedical research, but I still have interests in philosophy, especially in metaphysics, epistemology, and bioethics.
More about me Hobbies
 Playing the violin, both classically and covering more modern music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Towards a reductionist virtue ethic</title>
      <link>/posts/virtue-ethics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 22:52:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/virtue-ethics/</guid>
      <description>Over the last several decades, the field of virtue ethics has seen a resurgence in popularity. Alasdair Macintyre’s After Virtue drew significant attention for its critique of Enlightenment systems of morality (Macintyre, 75), but works by authors like Martha Nussbaum and Phillipa Foot have also brought significant focus upon theories of virtue. Philosophers differ, though, on how far they stray from Aristotle, the father of virtue ethics. Some take a more relativist approach to virtue theory, tying moral judgements and criteria to cultures and societies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Perdurantist Model of Time Travel</title>
      <link>/posts/time-travel-theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 22:52:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/time-travel-theory/</guid>
      <description>It seems that time travel may be metaphysically possible, since we can imagine it occurring. For example, envision the following: an intrepid scientist steps into a gleaming capsule in 2030, closes the door, and presses a button. In what seems to him to be a mere instant, his journey finishes and he arrives in the year 2031. Another scenario might involve a spacecraft that departs from Earth and travels close to the speed of light for what feels to its occupants like a mere 2 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>/docs/example-doc/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/example-doc/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is chapter 1 of example doc.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>/docs/example-doc/nested-chapter/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/example-doc/nested-chapter/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is chapter 1 of nested chapter.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>/docs/example-doc/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/example-doc/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is chapter 2 of example doc.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>/docs/example-doc/nested-chapter/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/example-doc/nested-chapter/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is chapter 2 of nested chapter.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/google281bd16dc279302f/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/google281bd16dc279302f/</guid>
      <description>google-site-verification: google281bd16dc279302f.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>/files/samuel_braza_cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/files/samuel_braza_cv/</guid>
      <description>Education Santa Clara University, B.S. Biochemistry, B.A. Philosophy. Santa Clara, CA.  Research Enveda Biosciences, Research Technician.  Drug discovery work aimed at discovering and testing pharmaceutically active compounds in plants. Helped develop and test proteomics and metabolomics protocols, using literature reviews to identify useful protocols that could be modified for current research needs. Performed various experiments on various cells and plant extracts.  Santa Clara University, Abbyad Lab. Research Assistant. -2020
 Research aimed at developing label-free sorting sorting systems, in order to quickly isolate metabolically-active cancer cells for genomic analysis, as well as sort enzymes based on activity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
